export const questionsArray = [
    {
        "category":"Music",
        "id":"622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff2a",
        "correctAnswer":"Michael Jackson",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Nicki Minaj","Neil Young","Eric Clapton"],
        "question":"The iconic song 'Thriller' was released by which musician?",
        "tags":["songs","musicians","1980's","general_knowledge","music"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {   "category":"Geography",
        "id":"623741f5cb85f7ce9e949d9b",
        "correctAnswer":"Portugal",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Kosovo","Cuba","Panama"],
        "question":"Lisbon is the capital city of which country?",
        "tags":["geography"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"History",
        "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f9503ba",
        "correctAnswer":"Babylon",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Atlantis","Jerusalem","Scythia"],
        "question":"Where were the Hanging Gardens?",
        "tags":["history"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false 
    },

    {
        "category":"Geography",
        "id":"62602db94b176d54800e3ca9",
        "correctAnswer":"United Kingdom",
        "incorrectAnswers":["United States","New Zealand","Ireland"],
        "question":"In which country is the city of Edinburgh?",
        "tags":["cities","europe","geography"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false     
    },

    {
        "category":"Music",
        "id":"6266bc38ff2394bd44dedfff",
        "correctAnswer":"Cello",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Castanets","Cymbal","Piccolo"],
        "question":"Which of these is a stringed instrument?",
        "tags":["music"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"Food & Drink",
        "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f95023e",
        "correctAnswer":"Haggis ",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Neeps and Tatties","Pizza Crunch","Cullen Skink"],
        "question":"Which Scottish Dish Is Boiled In The Stomach Lining Of A Sheep?",
        "tags":["food_and_drink"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"Geography",
        "id":"6237404acb85f7ce9e949cef",
        "correctAnswer":"Egypt",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Kuwait","Taiwan","Spain"],
        "question":"Cairo is the capital city of which country?",
        "tags":["geography"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"Music",
        "id":"622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff10",
        "correctAnswer":"Madonna",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Eric Clapton","Nicki Minaj","Alanis Morissette"],
        "question":"Which American singer and songwriter released the song 'Like a Virgin'?",
        "tags":["songs","musicians","general_knowledge","1980's","music"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"Music",
        "id":"622a1c397cc59eab6f950dc4",
        "correctAnswer":"The Beatles",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Deep Purple","Feeder","Uriah Heep"],
        "question":"Which band includes 'John Lennon'?",
        "tags":["music"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"Geography",
        "id":"62374081cb85f7ce9e949d05",
        "correctAnswer":"Germany",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Ukraine","Poland","Switzerland"],
        "question":"Berlin is the capital city of which country?",
        "tags":["capital_cities","general_knowledge","geography"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"Geography",
        "id":"6237406fcb85f7ce9e949cfe",
        "correctAnswer":"Paris",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Marseilles","Bordeaux","Monaco"],
        "question":"What is the capital city of France?",
        "tags":["general_knowledge","capital_cities","france","europe","cities","geography"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"Science",
        "id":"622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510c3",
        "correctAnswer":"23",
        "incorrectAnswers":["10","2","12"],
        "question":"How Many Pairs of Chromosomes Does The Average Human Have?",
        "tags":["numbers","anatomy","biology","science"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"Science",
        "id":"622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95100a",
        "correctAnswer":"The Universe",
        "incorrectAnswers":["The Milky Way","Andromeda","Infinity"],
        "question":"What was created with the big bang?",
        "tags":["physics","general_knowledge","science"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"History",
        "id":"622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c85",
        "correctAnswer":"Watergate",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Hotelgate","Croneygate","Corruptiongate"],
        "question":"What was the name of the scandal that forced President Nixon to resign?",
        "tags":["events","presidents","usa","history"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"Food & Drink",
        "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f9502e3",
        "correctAnswer":"Greece ",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Italy","Russia","Pakistan"],
        "question":"In which country would you expect to be served a yoghurt-based starter called 'tzatziki'?",
        "tags":["food_and_drink"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"Music",
        "id":"622a1c347cc59eab6f94fba1",
        "correctAnswer":"'Circle of Life' by Elton John",
        "incorrectAnswers":["\"SpongeBob SquarePants Theme\" by Painty the Pirate","\"Let's Go Crazy\" by Prince and The Revolution","\"What I Got\" by Sublime"],
        "question":"Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Nants ingonyama bagithi Baba / Sithi uhm ingonyama...\"?",
        "tags":["songs","lyrics","music"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"Geography",
        "id":"622a1c387cc59eab6f950adf",
        "correctAnswer":"Russia",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Bangladesh","Thailand","Cambodia"],
        "question":"Which of these countries borders People's Republic of China?",
        "tags":["geography"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"Music",
        "id":"622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff51",
        "correctAnswer":"Michael Jackson",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Nicki Minaj","Neil Young","Eric Clapton"],
        "question":"Which American singer released the song 'Wanna Be Startin' Somethin''?",
        "tags":["songs","music"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },

    {
        "category":"Food & Drink",
        "id":"622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951617",
        "correctAnswer":"100",
        "incorrectAnswers":["0","273","71"],
        "question":"At What Temperature Centigrade Does Water Boil At?",
        "tags":["food_and_drink"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    },
        
    {
        "category":"History",
        "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f9503fe",
        "correctAnswer":"Aqueduct",
        "incorrectAnswers":["Canal","Forum","Arena"],
        "question":"What did the Romans build to convey water?",
        "tags":["history"],
        "type":"Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "regions":[],
        "isNiche":false
    }
]